Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Cream Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the Frosted Animal
Cookie Blizzard. Let me show you how to
make it. For the base, we're doing a
vanilla cake batter base. So, high
protein milk, sweetener, salt, zantham
gum, some vanilla bean paste, and some
cake batter extract. And you can just
blend that up, throw it in the freezer
for at least 16 hours, and then take it
out and run it under hot water for about
a minute and throw it in your creamy on
the light ice cream setting. Now, let me
drop a little mixing hack. So, we all
know the Ninja Creamy obliterates
mixins. But what you don't know is that
if the mix-ins are hard enough, they
don't get broken up at all. So, I took
my frosted animal cookies and I crushed
them up by hand into my desired size.
And then I froze these pieces for about
an hour before I added them into the ice
cream. This allows the pieces to stay
whole, or at least at the size you want
them to be, instead of getting
absolutely obliterated. Quick bite.
That bust.